{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Refrigerator Service Pros","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62000/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62000,"taskName":"Refrigerator Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install or Repair a Fridge","xmTaskDescriptor":"Refrigerator Service Pros","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":141,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"refrigerator, fridge, hook up, hookup, icebox, cooler","textMessagingName":"Fridge","rolloverLongDesc":"Fridge install may include hooking it up to a water line for an ice-maker or filtered water dispenser.","rolloverShortDesc":"Either installing or repairing a refrigerator","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Install a Refrigerator.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Refrigerator Repair or Install \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fridge Repair Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":3,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Refrigerator Repair or Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Refigerator - Repair or Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Refrigerator Project","urlName":"Refrigerator-Repair-or-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Refrigerator Repair \u0026 Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"refrigerator, fridge, hook up, hookup, icebox, cooler","emcCategoryOid":-12003,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":8402,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62000/":{"taskOID":62000,"originalTaskOID":62000,"setID":8402,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500020,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"Type of Service","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203544,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install a new refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Install a new refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair a refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Repair a refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502605,"questionDisplayText":"For installs, what type is it?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For installs, what type is it?","shortQuestionText":"For installs, what type is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203632,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New fridge in the same location","answerDisplayText":"New fridge in the same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New fridge in a new location","answerDisplayText":"New fridge in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203633,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair a fridge","answerDisplayText":"Repair a fridge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5259,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Repairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For repairs, what best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2803,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gets too cold","answerDisplayText":"Gets too cold","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203548,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Doesn't get cold enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get cold enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203506,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Doesn't run at all","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't run at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203549,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ice-maker doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Ice-maker doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203550,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water dispenser doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Water dispenser doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500020,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of service do you need?","shortQuestionText":"Type of Service","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":203544,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install a new refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Install a new refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair a refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Repair a refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203544,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Install a new refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Install a new refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203545,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair a refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Repair a refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502605,"questionDisplayText":"For installs, what type is it?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For installs, what type is it?","shortQuestionText":"For installs, what type is it?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":203632,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New fridge in the same location","answerDisplayText":"New fridge in the same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New fridge in a new location","answerDisplayText":"New fridge in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203633,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair a fridge","answerDisplayText":"Repair a fridge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":203632,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New fridge in the same location","answerDisplayText":"New fridge in the same location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203546,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New fridge in a new location","answerDisplayText":"New fridge in a new location","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203633,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Repair a fridge","answerDisplayText":"Repair a fridge","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5259,"questionDisplayText":"Plumbing Repairs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"For repairs, what best describes the problem?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":2803,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gets too cold","answerDisplayText":"Gets too cold","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203548,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Doesn't get cold enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get cold enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203506,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Doesn't run at all","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't run at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203549,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ice-maker doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Ice-maker doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203550,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water dispenser doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Water dispenser doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2803,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Gets too cold","answerDisplayText":"Gets too cold","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203548,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Doesn't get cold enough","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't get cold enough","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203506,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Doesn't run at all","answerDisplayText":"Doesn't run at all","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203549,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ice-maker doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Ice-maker doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3504,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Leaking","answerDisplayText":"Leaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203550,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Water dispenser doesn't work","answerDisplayText":"Water dispenser doesn't work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}